{
    "subject": "resource/Sentrigo",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Sentrigo is located in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9800304770469666,
            "question": "Is Sentrigo based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.939651370048523,
            "question": "Where is Sentrigo located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.866051435470581,
            "question": "In which country is Sentrigo situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.853756308555603,
            "question": "Is Sentrigo an American company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7915540337562561,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Sentrigo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7623951435089111,
            "question": "According to the information, where is Sentrigo established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7429940104484558,
            "question": "Where can you find Sentrigo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.569475531578064,
            "question": "To which country does Sentrigo belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.473868191242218,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Sentrigo?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42768579721450806,
            "question": "Can you tell me the country of Sentrigo's operation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sentrigo is located in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6146_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of Sentrigo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6146_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country does Sentrigo belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6146_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find Sentrigo?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6146_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6146_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The text explicitly states that Sentrigo is located in Santa Clara, United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that \"Sentrigo is located in Santa Clara, United States,\" which supports the statement that Sentrigo is located in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}